AG Athena Gardner

CONTACT



PHONE

0211448275



EMAIL

athena536@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

I pride myself in being adaptable and have worked in various types of situations and working environments.

I find opportunities to learn in challenges and I see them as a way to practice my problemsolving skills. I have obtained some technical knowledge and experience communicating technical tasks within different sectors from many of my positions as well as when I took on the role of Project Liaison Officer for a web project within Manna.

KEY STRENGTHS

- Adaptable
- Problem solver
- Creative
- · Attention to detail
- Lifelong learner

URLs



https://www.linkedin.com/in/athena-gardner/



https://github.com/AthenaG536/



http://www.athena-gardner.com/

DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE

I love learning new languages & new techniques to utilize languages I'm familiar with. I have experience with various languages including but not limited to; Python, C#, Java, C++, SQL, HTML/CSS & JavaScript.

I also enjoy using Selenium IDE for automation testing and would love the opportunity to use this and to learn more about automation testing.

COMMUNICATION EXPERIENCE

During both my career & my studies I have done presentations & reports to a professional standard. I'm quite confident in preparing & running presentations while adjusting my terminology to my target audience and I've done these both individually & with team members.

WORK HISTORY

South Auckland Plumbing, Auckland (March 2021 - Current)

Freelancing Technical Writer (>6 months)

Manna Christian Stores, Auckland (December 2015 - July 2021)

- Information Technology Assistant (3 years, 2018 2021)
- Retail Store Manager (7 months, 2018)
- Order Picker (3 years, 2014 2018)

Supachick, Rotorua (February 2013 - October 2014)

Cashier (1 year 9 months)

I've worked closely with various people & in different environments. I have found that I am more productive working remotely and/or in smaller teams.

EDUCATION

United Institute of Technology, Auckland

Bachelor of Computing Systems BCS, (2018-present)

John Paul College, Rotorua (2008-2014)

- House Captain 2014
- NCEA Level 3
- Height Safety 2014
- Workplace Fire & Emergency Management 2014

REFERENCES

Natalia Nehring, Lecturer & Advisor Phone: + 64 9 815 4321 x 7592 Email: nnehring@unitec.ac.nz Kelly Setu, Marketing Manager & Colleague

Phone: + 64 27 5222387 Email: kelly@manna.co.nz